

CONTACT



+5493482 445015



emcon84@gmail.com



https://emcon-dev.vercel.app/



<u>Whatsapp</u>



<u>Telegram</u>

SKILLS

- Design with Adobe Suite
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- NextJs
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind

LANGUAGE

English Basic

EMILIANO CONTI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

With 3 years of experience in the systems area of a national company, working as a frontend for a wholesale ecommerce, and 8 months as a frontend for a startup, where I work as an integrator of analytical tools, web designer and developer of mobile and web apps.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer and systems technical support Intercap SRL - June 2018 - December 2021

Working as a web developer, I had the task of maintaining a b2b ecommerce, with Java as the backend of the system and Bootstrap as the together with PrimeFaces as the front framework for Java. Also tasks such as technical support and hardware maintenance, such as notebooks and internal PCs of the company as well as servers.

Frontend developer

Oliver Pets - December 2021 - currently

In Oliver enter as an integrator of analytical tools such as Clevertap to an ecommerce system based on PHP. Then I worked as a layout designer of an App made in React Native, working with Figma and passing the designs to code. Today I find myself working as Frontend in web development of the company, and internal platforms, with technologies such as React and NextJs

EDUCATION AND COURSES

Computer Systems Programmer 2009 - 2011

Graphic design course held in 2012

Programming course with Angular and NodeJs (Udemy - 2018)

Html and CSS course on Platzi platform - 2019

Doing React course with MERN stack (Udemy)